let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does a triangular sign with a red border and a white exclamation mark indicate in European traffic rules?",
    answer: "C) Warning Sign",
    options: [
      "A) Yield Sign",
      "B) No Entry Sign",
      "C) Warning Sign",
      "D) Priority Road Sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In most European countries, what does a yellow traffic light indicate?",
    answer: "B) Proceed with caution",
    options: [
      "A) Prepare to stop",
      "B) Proceed with caution",
      "C) Stop immediately",
      "D) Slow down and be prepared to stop"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the maximum permitted blood alcohol concentration (BAC) limit for drivers in most European countries?",
    answer: "B) 0.08%",
    options: [
      "A) 0.05%",
      "B) 0.08%",
      "C) 0.02%",
      "D) 0.10%"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does a blue circular road sign with a white car and two arrows in opposite directions indicate?",
    answer: "D) Motorway",
    options: [
      "A) Parking Area",
      "B) One-Way Street",
      "C) Roundabout",
      "D) Motorway"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In most European countries, what does a dashed white line in the middle of the road indicate?",
    answer: "B) Overtaking Allowed",
    options: [
      "A) No Overtaking",
      "B) Overtaking Allowed",
      "C) No Parking Zone",
      "D) Pedestrian Crossing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What does a red triangle road sign with a black cross inside indicate?",
    answer: "D) Stop",
    options: [
      "A) Give Way",
      "B) No Parking",
      "C) No Entry",
      "D) Stop"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In European traffic rules, what color are the signs that indicate mandatory directions on motorways?",
    answer: "B) Blue",
    options: [
      "A) Green",
      "B) Blue",
      "C) Red",
      "D) Yellow"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does a circular blue sign with a white arrow pointing upwards indicate in European traffic rules?",
    answer: "D) Mandatory Direction",
    options: [
      "A) Exit Ahead",
      "B) No Entry",
      "C) Pedestrian Crossing",
      "D) Mandatory Direction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In European traffic rules, what does a white rectangular sign with red border and a black pictogram of a camera indicate?",
    answer: "D) Speed Enforcement Camera",
    options: [
      "A) Speed Limit Zone",
      "B) Traffic Signal Ahead",
      "C) Police Checkpoint",
      "D) Speed Enforcement Camera"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the minimum age requirement for driving a car in most European countries?",
    answer: "C) 18 years",
    options: [
      "A) 16 years",
      "B) 17 years",
      "C) 18 years",
      "D) 21 years"
    ]
  }
];
